Guide to the
Brown University Library
Default Call Number
John Hay Library University Archives and Manuscripts Box A Brown University Providence, RI, 02912 Telephone: Manuscripts: 401-863-3723; University Archives: 401-863-2148 Email: Manuscripts: hay@brown.edu; University Archives: archives@brown.edu
Biographical/Historical Note
Collection information
There are no restrictions on access, except that the collection can only be seen by prior appointment. Some materials may be stored off-site and cannot be produced on the same day on which they are requested.
- GOTNG Triangle Publishing Prize Acceptance Talk.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/7/7/1/Attachments/177824/1/Date created: 2015-10-03 13:54:10 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-03 13:54:10 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW_chapter 6 Sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 6 SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX SEX/Date created: 2012-06-30 04:39:31 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-06-30 05:42:37 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- QPD Page Proof Attachments.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Notes on QPD Page Proofs/Date created: 2011-11-26 15:25:20 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-11-26 15:53:01 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Politics of Desire 1.0.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/Politics of Desire/Date created: 2012-01-24 18:07:02 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-01-24 18:39:17 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- IC_Kate Bornstein completed.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/St. Luke's-Roosevelt/Date created: 2012-07-10 14:00:12 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-10 14:02:55 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Urbana Trip 0913-20 schedule.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Urbana Ill Sep 2013/Date created: 2013-09-09 23:11:39 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-09-09 23:13:05 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Ecstasy Is Necessary Review KB 1st Draft.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/7/7/1/Attachments/177701/2/Date created: 2015-10-03 13:53:05 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-03 13:53:05 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW chapter 9 sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 9/Date created: 2012-06-30 05:47:38 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-06-30 05:48:57 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Old Exercises Where Gender Is.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 9/Chapter 8 resources/Date created: 2012-04-12 14:32:15 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-04-12 14:32:15 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- TOTWK_by_KB_OutMag.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/TOd Trannies W Knives/Date created: 2010-04-15 16:19:01 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-04-22 19:29:04 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Dixie Belle Reader 2011.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/7/7/1/Attachments/177401/1/Date created: 2015-10-03 13:53:51 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-03 13:53:51 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Intro All That Jazz.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/All That Jazz at IFC Center/Date created: 2011-07-25 17:04:39 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-07-25 17:15:46 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Newlyweds.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Gender Complete/Fictionmania Downloads/Date created: 2010-11-26 21:39:42 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-11-26 21:43:36 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 20 Questions.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/interviews, essays, talks/Date created: 2012-04-14 10:40:33 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-09 20:38:44 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Vested Interests Review.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Bay Area Reporter/Book Reviews/Date created: 2011-05-21 15:39:47 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-21 15:39:47 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Figments of Erotic Imagination-KB Pass.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Barbara Words/Date created: 2012-09-30 19:26:07 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-09-30 19:26:07 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- text to grab for so made a man.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Book 2 Chap 5/how the sea org made a man out of me ƒ/Date created: 2008-09-07 17:48:04 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-02-03 12:13:09 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-4 where it gets complicated-tighter.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/3-4 OK This Is Where It Gets Complicated/3-4 Round One/Date created: 2011-06-10 15:14:12 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-06-10 15:38:50 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 1 KB Edit TOC thru Chap 1.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/My New Gender Workbook - 1st Proofs for KB/Date created: 2013-01-15 16:46:24 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-01-15 19:25:50 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 5.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 5 There's Only One Gender—Yours/Date created: 2012-03-07 11:56:03 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-06-30 03:21:15 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Transgender Day Remembrance 09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/Articles to Mine for MNGW/Date created: 2009-11-19 12:10:46 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-11-20 01:35:36 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Buffalo Night by Caitlin.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/caitlin/Date created: 2009-01-18 01:14:28 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-01-18 01:14:29 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- letter to jess.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Letter to Jessica Op Ed/Date created: 2012-06-12 01:44:49 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-06-12 14:44:43 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Two Forms of ID.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Gender Complete/Fictionmania Downloads/Date created: 2010-11-26 18:35:30 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-11-26 19:07:30 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Kate Bornstein Contract.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Attic Gigs/UNLV/Date created: 2009-09-29 13:59:20 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-09-29 13:59:20 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Bornstein's Theory of Relativity KB pass Pages 09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Mine Me for Transition Pieces/Brevity Mag/Date created: 2015-04-05 13:38:27 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-04-05 13:38:27 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- We Three for the Book.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Pictures/Graphic Work In Progress/Justin 50/Date created: 2013-05-09 15:00:48 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-05-09 15:00:48 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- GoFundMe Comments.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Kate Stay Alive/Date created: 2013-03-21 13:07:12 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-03-21 13:07:12 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Cast List Inherit the Earth.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Inherit The Earth/Date created: 2009-07-03 12:35:47 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-07-08 18:43:29 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Cover Sketch 2 by KB .pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/KB Cover Sketches/Date created: 2012-08-22 21:25:03 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-08-22 22:27:52 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- book-spine.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Layout & Design/QueerPleasantCover ƒ/Date created: 2011-05-27 23:18:35 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-27 23:33:11 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Rainbow w Ruby Slippers.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/KB Cover Sketches/Date created: 2012-08-23 17:29:14 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-08-23 17:29:14 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- book 3.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/for alan/Date created: 2011-09-07 15:08:53 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-07 15:08:53 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Please Read Me First.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/0/8/1/Attachments/180426/2/Date created: 2015-10-03 13:52:24 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-03 13:52:24 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Letter to Librarian Galley Readers.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/~Memoir PR/Blurber Letters/Date created: 2012-01-20 15:35:59 EST-0500Date modified: 2012-01-20 15:43:23 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 10 MNGW Chapter 10.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Final Draft KB->Routledge/Chapters—Apple Pages/Date created: 2012-06-27 13:55:50 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-15 15:23:22 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 7 MNGW_chapter 7_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Final Draft KB->Routledge/Chapters—Apple Pages/Date created: 2012-06-21 11:47:31 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-15 11:54:26 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-5 Girl KB pass 2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Book Three/Date created: 2011-08-19 13:47:29 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-19 13:57:20 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Outlaws Last Gleaning.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Gender Outlaw Next Gen/Date created: 2010-03-06 11:22:50 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-03-09 01:42:13 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- A Queer and Pleasant Danger GOLD.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Date created: 2011-09-13 20:11:05 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-13 20:11:05 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Princess book proposal.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/The Princess Book/Date created: 2011-07-19 14:55:32 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-07-19 14:55:33 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- UCD_keynote_BC.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Completed Articles & Talks/DUBLIN Lesbian Lives 08 w Barbara/Date created: 2009-03-24 20:42:04 EDT-0400Date modified: 2009-03-24 20:42:04 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-1 Alpha Draft In Progress.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Book 3 Chapter 1/Date created: 2010-04-27 17:19:13 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-05-09 17:58:46 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Seasonal_8.5x11.AddressLabel_centered_6.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Pictures/Graphic Work In Progress/2009 Xmas Journal Collage/Date created: 2009-12-20 14:12:16 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-12-20 14:12:16 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- You Me and Gender BC PASS.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Trans For the Fun of It/Book/0. to be sorted/Date created: 2017-04-04 21:08:45 EDT-0400Date modified: 2017-04-04 21:08:45 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Kate proposal.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/~Memoir PR/Gail Leondar-Wright QPD/Date created: 2012-04-30 12:20:45 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-04-30 12:20:45 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- David Harrison My experiences on the CSETI Training.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/David Harrison/Date created: 2010-04-22 17:27:04 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-04-22 17:28:14 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW BW if it were KBs notebook.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/KB Cover Sketches/Date created: 2012-08-23 19:42:07 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-08-23 19:44:57 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- gleanersGOTNG.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/Gender Outlaw Next Gen/Date created: 2010-01-05 15:02:20 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-03-06 13:20:01 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Quotes About KB.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Kate B 4U/Blurbs & Bios/Date created: 2013-07-21 23:22:06 EDT-0400Date modified: 2017-07-23 21:04:46 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Justin V PS 122 Tribute.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Correspondence, Blurbs, & Referrals/Date created: 2011-04-25 16:18:47 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-04-26 18:15:29 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- MNGW Chapter 10 sketch.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Chapter 10/Date created: 2012-06-30 10:26:27 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-06-30 10:28:05 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Ltr Recc Crystal Yakacki OHSU.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Correspondence, Blurbs, & Referrals/Crystal Yakacki/Date created: 2010-10-12 11:15:27 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-10-12 13:47:44 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Carroll University NCOD 2010.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/y2kate & TTB/KB Touring Pieces folder/~~current/Date created: 2010-10-19 22:09:21 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-10-19 22:56:13 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- NY State Collection Letter June 2011.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Kate Bornstein Financial/Older Finances/New York State Taxes/Date created: 2011-06-21 10:28:40 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-06-21 11:08:29 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- TWEETS ETC.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/~Pages for MNGW/Date created: 2012-05-22 12:33:19 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-05-22 13:25:30 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Timed Talk—Save This As Template.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Cleaned Desktop Files/Office/Date created: 2011-10-29 23:24:14 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-10-29 23:24:14 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- B survey letter pages 09.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Barbara Words/Date created: 2016-01-14 21:59:47 EST-0500Date modified: 2016-01-14 21:59:47 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Elon University 041112 itinerary.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Venues/Elon University Apr 2012/Date created: 2012-04-09 20:02:19 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-04-09 20:03:33 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Text for Cover Proposal.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Layout & Design/Date created: 2011-06-26 22:36:20 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-06-27 00:00:51 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Letter to Oxford re Deductible Year.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/kb-health-dropbox/kb-health to 2012/Date created: 2010-12-15 14:06:42 EST-0500Date modified: 2010-12-15 17:39:55 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- queer and pleasant danger book 3 for Scrivener.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/Edits Back & Forth/Book Three/Date created: 2011-08-19 12:51:44 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-19 12:52:25 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 316 HSESITTER INSTRUC Aug2011.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/house-sitting/Date created: 2011-08-10 15:01:52 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-08-10 15:30:10 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Chapt. #1-The Ecstatic Experience Vs2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/In Others Words/Barbara Words/BC Ecstasy Is Neccessary/Date created: 2011-03-10 22:57:41 EST-0500Date modified: 2011-03-10 22:57:41 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- IRS Payment Letter Sep 2011.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Dropbox/Kate Bornstein Financial/Older Finances/IRS Payment Agreement/Monthly Payments to IRS/Date created: 2011-09-13 14:46:04 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-13 14:48:17 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Talking Points Post-Trans March.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/Touring/Pride/Toronto Trans Pride 2011/Date created: 2011-07-01 14:20:11 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-07-03 11:49:30 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 7 KB Edit Chap 7.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/My New Gender Workbook - 1st Proofs for KB/Date created: 2013-01-17 16:13:45 EST-0500Date modified: 2013-01-17 16:38:45 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- Intros for Guests JE Party.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Library/Mail/V5/27F8CF84-27C9-45EB-BBC2-180B448CB245/Sent Messages.mbox/7FC563F4-99CD-45EC-AFCA-5A7ABA6D9DF2/Data/5/8/1/Attachments/185018/2/Date created: 2015-10-23 12:04:27 EDT-0400Date modified: 2015-10-23 12:04:27 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-4 where it gets complicated.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/3-4 OK This Is Where It Gets Complicated/3-4 Round One/Date created: 2011-06-09 14:36:25 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-06-09 20:32:39 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-3 Stages Of Life.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/~~ First Draft ~~/Date created: 2011-05-05 16:19:09 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-05 16:21:29 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 9 MNGW_chapter 9_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/My New Gender Workbook/MNGW Final Draft KB->Routledge/Chapters—Apple Pages/Date created: 2012-06-21 18:42:37 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-07-15 12:11:30 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 2-5.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/~~ First Draft ~~/Date created: 2009-12-29 19:08:45 EST-0500Date modified: 2009-12-30 00:24:01 EST-0500MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- climbing the foremast.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Dixon Place Launch/Readings for Dixon Place/Date created: 2012-04-29 17:55:43 EDT-0400Date modified: 2012-04-29 17:55:43 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 3-3 Stages Of Life - 2.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/old words from young me/QPD Memoir/Attic Queer & Pleasant/3-3 Under Construction/Date created: 2011-05-05 10:56:32 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-05-05 16:18:22 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- ePub Best Practices for Pages.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Music/iTunes/iTunes Music/TV Shows/Downloads/Date created: 2010-08-27 12:46:57 EDT-0400Date modified: 2010-08-27 12:46:57 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- kb half page ad.pages
  Original directory: /Users/starbuck/Pictures/Graphic Work In Progress/Booking Ad 2013/Date created: 2013-08-11 19:55:30 EDT-0400Date modified: 2013-08-12 13:04:04 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
- 5 MNGW Chapter 5 KB pass.pages